admissionnews.com 2015-11-03

# Privacy Policy:::Admissionnews.com

Privacy is the base of trust between you and AmissionNews.

Complete confidentiality is maintained with AmissionNews and it is assured that no information is leaked to. The information is strictly for an excellent collaboration of you and us for better business for today and tomorrow. The information collected from the registration form that is presented to users when they choose to register may include contact information such as the user's name, gender, e-mail address, contact details, postal address, profession and country. Information collected by Site during registration also includes but is not restricted to Educational Information including preferred educational courses and destinations, education level, marks obtained, expected year of admission and the profile of the registrant (student/parent).

The Site reserves the right to use the user information collected during the registration process or otherwise to use for carrying out its own analysis and research. The Site also reserves the right to provide this information to its business partners / relevant third party for any consideration, including monetary gains. The Site also reserves the right to contact the user based upon the information provided. This contact may be initiated by any of the possible means on the basis of the information provided by the student at registration or through any other mode of contact. 

Any user not agreeable to the aforementioned policy shall not register himself/herself with the site. By registering with the site or by the way of filling up any form requiring user information, the user is deemed to have agreed to this privacy policy of the Site. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**  
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

In addition, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to our site. Google's use of the **Dart cookie** enables it to serve ads to visitors based on visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Visitors may opt out of the Dart cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Google may use interest based advertising where they recognize the types of web pages users visit across the Adsense network. This helps advertisers reach users on the basis of their interests. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
The terms of this privacy policy are subject to change from time to time without any prior notice. 

**Contact Information**  
We welcome your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. Should there be any concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy, We will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same.
